http://interpraxis.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy
Policy
a. What information of yours does InterPraxis collect?
The Site collects two types of information, “anonymous information” and “personal information”. Anonymous information refers to information that is not about an identifiable individual. Each time a visitor comes to the Site, InterPraxis may collect information that is necessary to improve the overall quality of the visitor’s online experience. InterPraxis may collect computer and connection information such as the visitor’s IP address (e.g., whether the user is logged on from a .ca, .com, .gov or .edu domain), referral data, and browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform). InterPraxis collects this user information for purposes of providing the Site. In addition to this anonymous information, InterPraxis may also collect information that is about an identifiable individual (“personal information”). Personal information includes information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name and e-mail address. Wherever and whenever InterPraxis collects personal information we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.
b. Personal information collection. InterPraxis collects personal information in the following ways from different parts of the Site:
(I) Personal information is gathered when you voluntarily supply information to the Site. You can choose whether or not to provide InterPraxis with your personal information. If you choose not to provide the requested information, InterPraxis may not be able to offer you some of the Products and Services that depend on this type of information to function.
(II) If you contact InterPraxis through e-mail, we may keep a record of that correspondence. We do not sell any email addresses of those who communicate with us via email or share those with others for non-related communications. We use the information provided only so that we may communicate with you electronically.
c. What organization is collecting the information?
When you provide personal information at the site, InterPraxis Consulting is the entity collecting that information.
d. How is personal information used?
Any personal information you provide to InterPraxis is maintained and accessible only by InterPraxis, unless specifically stated otherwise. InterPraxis may use the information it collects to deliver the services requested. InterPraxis may also use personal information if it has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful when investigating a contravention of a federal, provincial or foreign law; for an emergency that threatens an individual’s life, health or security; if the use is clearly in the individual’s interest and consent is not available in a timely way; or if knowledge and consent would compromise the availability or accuracy of the information and collection is required to investigate a breach of an agreement or contravention of a federal, provincial or foreign law. InterPraxis may disclose personal information
(I) to an advocate or notary or a barrister or solicitor who is representing it;
(II) if required to comply with a legal or legislative obligation;
(III) to a government institution or part of a government institution that has made a request for the information, identified its lawful authority to obtain the information. InterPraxis may disclose personal information to its agents, suppliers and service providers in conjunction with providing you with products, services or operating portions of the Site. Such entities will be required to use personal information provided solely for such purposes. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services.
e. How can you change or delete your information?
InterPraxis will allow you to change or delete your personal information. Currently, to change or delete your personal information, please contact InterPraxis as described on the Site.
×
Close
